dropshipzone.com.au 2018-08-12

# Privacy Statement

We respect your privacy and we are committed to protecting your privacy and to complying with the National Privacy Principles in the Australia Privacy Act. We only collect personal information that is necessary to conduct our business as an online supplier.

**Information that Dropshipzone May Collect Online**

The circumstances of collection and the type of service you request from us determine the range of personal information we collect from you. For placing an order, Dropshipzone requires your personal contact information including name, email address, delivery address, telephone numbers; and personal billing information such as credit card or debit card details and billing address. 

**How is information collected**

Your personal information could be collected while you visit our website, when you deal with us over the telephone, send us correspondence (could be by letter, fax or email), or when you have contact with us in person. No personal information will be collected by us without your consent. We consider that your consent is granted when you complete the fields necessary to facilitate a transaction through this website.

**Purpose of Collecting Information**

We collect aggregated information about you to facilitate your access to our website and deliver products you have ordered from us. Additionally, we will use the information to conduct marketing report and activities, collect your opinion on our products, services, marketing and website, and send you a newsletter regularly.

We endeavour to ensure, where possible, the security and integrity of your personal information. Unfortunately we cannot guarantee 100% the security of any information you transmit to us since it is being transmitted over the internet. Once any information is in our possession, Dropshipzone requires employees to respect customers’ privacy consistent with our legal responsibilities. We are committed to treat your information with the utmost care. We assure you that none of your personal information will be disclosed unless it is required or authorised by law. We will take all reasonable precautions to protect your personal information from any alteration or illegal use.

**Keeping Your Personal Information Up To Date**

You are entitled to gain access to personal information that Dropshipzone holds about you. If the information we hold about you is inaccurate, incomplete or out-of-date, please contact us and we will take reasonable steps to either correct the information, or if necessary, discuss alternative actions with you.

If you would like to unsubscribe from receiving any of our commercial electronic messages sent by Dropshipzone, please login to your account to make the change.

**Link to Other Sites**

This website contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Dropshipzone. Dropshipzone is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We recommend you read the privacy statement in each website you visit.

**Computer Tracking and Cookies**

We might use cookies for purposes such as keeping track of your preferences and profile information. Cookies are commonly used for marketing activities such as analysing user preferences and popular categories to strengthen the functionality and relevancy of our website.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Statement may change from time to time. You will be notified on the website for any changes to our Privacy Statement. You are therefore encouraged to review it frequently.
